<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bet Winner</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    //pasta
    <string name="pastaIngredients">Sports betting</string>
    <string name="pastaDesc">1xBet offers many additional markets on specific events: European handicap,
        correct score, run of play, over/under, team to score first etc.
        We also have a great selection of markets on international games on a club and country level.</string>
    //maggi
    <string name="maggiIngredients">App Bonuses</string>
    <string name="maggieDesc">Live bets are available 24 hours a day. For most sports,
        more than 30 markets are offered for each event,
        including bets on corners, yellow cards, free kicks etc.</string>
    //cake
    <string name="cakeIngredients">Social networks</string>
    <string name="cakeDesc">1xBet Sportsbook includes over 1,000 events daily.
        You can bet on a variety of popular sports: football, tennis, basketball, volleyball,
        ice hockey, golf, boxing, handball, American football, hockey, baseball, table tennis,
        biathlon, Aussie rules and bandy. We also offer bets on cricket, snooker, Formula 1,
        cycling, ski jumping, curling, floorball, inline hockey and water polo.
        With 1xBet, you can bet on more than 1,000 sporting events every day.</string>
    //pancake
    <string name="pancakeIngredients">One-click registrationa</string>
    <string name="pancakeDesc">You can top up your account at 1xBet betting shops.
        We also accept e-payments via WebMoney, Qiwi and others.

Winnings are paid out through the same method that was used to make a deposit.</string>
    //pizza
    <string name="pizzaIngredients">Site Services</string>
    <string name="pizzaDesc">Besides being a world-famous sports betting site and online casino,
        the 1xbet growth strategy can be taught to entrepreneurship students all over the world!
        This site was launched in 2011, and in just 10 years,
        1xbet English has been able to compete with the online gambling industry giants!
        Thanks to its exceptional advantages, the constant pursuit of developing its offerings,
        and the tremendous capabilities it has when compared with any other online gambling site.</string>
    //burgers
    <string name="burgerIngredients">1xbet English</string>
    <string name="burgerDesc">1xbet app holds the Curaçao committee license and supports more than 40 global languages.
        It is also remarkable that it provides support to its clients in all languages ​​as well.
        1x bet English contains more than a million active users. Despite these tremendous advantages that 1x bet apps offer,
        the minimum deposit is only $1! While there are many other bookmakers and online casinos
        that do not offer this huge number of benefits while their minimum deposit is $20 or more!</string>
    //fries
    <string name="friesIngredients">Safety</string>
    <string name="friesDesc">Moreover, 1xbet English makes good use of the novel technology potential.
        It offers an application 1x bet app for Android and IOS. Presents free live-stream matches in all sports.
        Sports punters also will be glad to know that the bookmaker
        features more than 1,000 odds daily for all sports with low margins. Also,
        casino games buffs will find more than 3,0000 games powered by more than 100 global developers.
\nMaggi is ready!</string>


</resources>